# MARCUS HALL

# **Oracle certified Full stack Developer**

**+1-234-253-6506** San Fransisco, CA

@ danette.eastwood@gmail.com

github.io/danette.east

## **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Developer with over 10 years of experience in Java/JS, Angular, Vue, React, Python, NumPy, SciPy, Scikit-learn. Led development of \$500K research project which was deemed a "gold standard" by the client. Increased client's revenue 2-fold after fine-tuning AI/ML-based algorithms. Well-acquainted with HR methodologies.

### **EDUCATION**

## M.S. in Computer Science

**Stanford Unversity** 

苗 2008 - 2009 👂 Palo Alto, CA

GPA 3.9 / 4.0

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Senior Full stack Developer

#### **Boyle**

🗰 2018 - Present 👂 San Fransisco, CA

Boyle is an international Technology and Management Consulting Group with a rapid pace development and innovative solutions for demanding projects. I work as a full-stack developer here, responsible for building, deploying and maintaining internal web applications.

- · Hired, trained and leading an Agile team of 7 full-stack developers
- Developed indexed database architecture using SQL procedures and triggers for 10 different applications
- Worked with Core Java to develop automated solutions to include web interfaces using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Web services
- Worked with a committee of 6 members to organise fun-activities for the employees

#### Full Stack Developer

#### Lauzon

苗 2013 - 2018 👂 San Fransisco, CA

Lauzon is a universal digital loyalty program that offers unique and fun rewards at the places you love.

- · Hired, trained and lead Agile team of 7 full-stack developers
- Simultaneously created & maintained scheduled jobs in SQL Server for space maintenance and daily backups of system and user databases for 10 clients
- Increased company revenue by 30% within 2 months after developing and implementing business logic for over 20 features
- Designed and Developed UI design for over 15 clients using CSS, HTML, ASP.NET, Vue, and React; websites scoring over 85 on Lighthouse

#### **Solution Architect**

#### **Keeling Group**

Keeling Group is a leading Digital Product Studio in California, helping companies to thrive on mobile apps, the web, VR/AR and IoT.

- Shortened project timeline by 14 months for company's largest customer by managing relationship with 3rd party vendors, saving over \$800K
- · Led development of \$500K research project which was deemed a "gold standard" by the client
- Fine-tuned and developed AI/ML-based algorithms based on the results with Scikit-learn, increasing revenue 2-fold
- Performed Web Scraping over a catalog of 100K+ school supply products using mainly NodeJS and MongoDB; completed in 1 month

#### **SKILLS**

#### Client-Side

HTML	CSS	JS	Angular
React	Vue	Redux	TypeScript
Backbone		Bootstrap	
		·	_

#### Server-side

Python Nu		nPy :	SciPy	
Scikit-lea	arn _	Keras	Eli5	
TensorFlow		MySQL	Noc	leJS
Redis	AWS	Mon	goDB	Spark
HTTP/2	_			

## Development & Operations

JUnit	NUnit	PyUnit	TestCafe			
Mocha	Jest	Scrum	Agile			
GIT Azure DevOps						

## CERTIFICATION

#### **Certified Agile Practitioner**

**PMI**, 2015

**AWS Solutions Architect - Associate Level** 

Amazon Web Services, 2013

**Java Development Certified Professional** 

Oracle, 2010

## **PROJECTS**

## OpenFlow based Firewall

https://github.com/danette.east/OpenFlow-Firewall OpenFlow protocol-based proactive Firewall in Python and NodeJS.

- Configured static rules using MD-SAL
- Engineered proactive rule evaluation system at OSI layer 7 using POX controller
- · Provided flexibility to configure rule using centralised NodeJS based GUI

# **STRENGTHS**

# Team Leadership

Introduction to Leadership course by **Harvard** 

## Communication

Attended a Communication course at **Stanford**.